ROEY REGEV | רועי רגב

Graphic design: UI/UX | motion | animation | storytelling | (coding)

ABOUT ME

An odd creature in the design world (at least that's how I feel). A versatile designer with marketing & product experience, business management education and some coding knowledge that likes to help building products in any way that is needed. Plus, I tend to stay in places I love for a long time.

+972-54-4560099

roeyregev@gmail.com ☑

Givatayim, Israel ☆

• •

SKILLS

- Storytelling Simplifying and conveying complex concepts to the client/user
- High professional versatility
- High level understanding of the integration between business, dev & design / (needs, goals, limits etc.)
- High learning skills. I figure out things. I vision the goal and learn what I need in order to create it.
- Applying motion and animation into the UI flow as an integrated enhancing part of the user experience and product storytelling.
- Experience in the startup life/ evolution throughout it's various phases (highs & lows)
- Strong opinions, low ego, open mind, patient demeanor
- Adorable

TECHNICAL SKILLS

- Figma & Sketch
- Adobe CC (with focus on After Effects, Photoshop and Illustrator)
- Html, CSS, SCSS, React, NextJS, Angular, Javascript, Node-js, MySQL

EDUCATION

2005-2009 - B. Design & Education - Wizo Design Academy

2017-2019 - MA Business Management (Technology, Innovation & Entrepreneurship) - TAU

Feb 2023- Feb 2024 - Full Stack Development course - John Bryce Academy

WORK EXPERIENCE

2018-present - Stuff That Works

Stuffthatworks.health

- UI/UX (web & iOS) designing new feature & adjusting existing features as the product evolved
- · Working closely with the dev team
- Educational & promotional animations, UI motion design, social media campaigns, ads campaigns, board/business presentations
- Anything that was needed in a small startup to help push the product/company forward.

2010-2018 - Waze/Google

- Mainly marketing design educational & promotional animations, motion design, social media campaigns, ads campaigns
- But also UI/UX (web, iOS, Android) and working with the dev team

2009-2010 - Not From Here branding studio

notfromhere.net

• Junior designer - Logos, branding, web pages, printed assets

ACHIEVEMENTS

2017 - Best marketing animation clip (Welcome to Waze Map Editor)

- Assif contest - Animix animation festival, Tel Aviv

• •